netpointinsurance.com 2016-05-10

# Privacy Policy - NetPointInsurance

NetPointInsurance.com, Inc. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personally identifiable information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions.  This privacy prolicy covers the site ([www.netpointinsurance.com](http://netpointinsurance.com/)).

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should first contact Customer Service by calling 717-441-9357 by email: [info@insurancenewsnet.com](mailto:info@insurancenewsnet.com) or by mail: NetPointInsurance.com, 3500 Market Street, Ste 202 Camp Hill, PA 17011. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).

## Uses of Information

**Newsletter Registration**  
In order to receive our email newsletters, you must first complete the registration form and provide your contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.

You have the option to provide demographic information (such as occupation, production level, experience, etc) to us; we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our site.

NetPointInsurance.com, Inc. (INN) is the sole owner of the information collected on netpointinsurance.com. INN collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [info@insurancenewsnet.com](mailto:info@insurancenewsnet.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Orders

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, company name, email, and billing address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

### Billing Agents

We use an outside credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

### Surveys

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes insurance sales practices, experience, income and other demographic information (such as gender, zip code, etc).

We use this information for compiling research and creating research reports. We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys; that company is prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

### Refer an Associate

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. NetPointInsurance.com, Inc. does not store this information; it is for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email [and tracking the success of our referral program].

Your referral’s contact information will not be captured or written to any database.

## Communications from the Site

### Special Offers and Updates

We will occasionally send you information on important news updates, premium subscription specials, magazine offers or insurance product offerings. You can sign up for these emails from us on our registration page.

Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out.”

### Newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section.

### Service-related Announcements

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

### Customer Service

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

### Profile

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, to create a “profile” of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information, and [or] your purchasing history, to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored content and to improve the content of the site for you.

### Personally identifiable information

We **DO NOT** Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties except as described in this privacy policy.

### Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name.  We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial.  If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [info@insurancenewsnet.com](http://netpointinsurance.com/info@netpointinsurance.com).

### Legal Disclaimer

We may also disclose your personally identifiable information:

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

### Choice/Opt-out

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [info@insurancenewsnet.com](mailto:info@insurancenewsnet.com). We offer an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications on our [Subscription Update Page](http://netpointinsurance.com/subscription_update.aspx), or you may contact us via...

### Telephone

717-441-9357

### Email

[info@insurancenewsnet.com](http://netpointinsurance.com/info@netpointinsurance.com) or

### Postal Mail

NetPointInsurance.com  
3500 Market Street, Ste 202  
Camp Hill, PA 17011s

### Log Files

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance and customize their experience on our site.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as premium content areas will be limited.

### Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

Our third party web analytics partner employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see “Choice and Opt-out.”

The use of cookies by our partners and tracking utility company is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners and tracking utility company use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [Here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

### Links to Other Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by NetPointInsurance.com, Inc. Please be aware that we, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

### Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook button and Widgets, such as the Twitter button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy policy applies only to information collected by this Web site.

### Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may [correct, update, delete or deactivate it] by making the change on our member information page:

[https://www.netpointinsurance.com/subscription_update.aspx](http://netpointinsurance.com/subscription_update.aspx) or by contacting Customer Service by calling: 717-441-9357, email: [info@insurancenewsnet.com](mailto:info@insurancenewsnet.com) or by mail:

NetPointInsurance.com  
3500 Market Street, Ste 202  
Camp Hill, PA 17011

### Security

The security of your personally identifiable information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can email us at: [info@insurancenewsnet.com](mailto:info@insurancenewsnet.com).

### Business Transitions

In the event NetPointInsurance.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personally identifiable information as well as any choices you may have regarding your personally identifiable information.

### Changes in this Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the changes taking effect.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

NetPointInsurance.com, Inc.

3500 Market Street, Ste 202  
Camp Hill, PA 17011  
717-441-9357
